(清明)もう 何も見えぬ｡
たった一つ…｡
また 目が
くらんでしまったらしい｡
道満… どうやら ﾜｼは➡
道満！ 来るがいい！
すべてを見通す目など
ﾜｼには もういらぬ！
ｱｲﾂの笑顔が見られれば
それでいい！
結野衆頭目 結野清明の真の力
とくと見せてやる！
♪♪～
I can no longer see...
Doman, it appears that I've
lost sight of myself again.
I no longer have a need to watch over all!
I only want one thing...
I only want to see her smile...
That's all.
Come get me, Doman!
I shall show you the true power of the head
of the Ketsuno clan, Seimei Ketsuno!
["Never Losing That Smile"]
[ﾏｲｸ]な… なんという力だ～!!
What incredible power!
Seimei has gathered the power
that was used to protect Edo!
[ﾏｲｸ]清明選手 江戸守護に配した力を
すべて ここに集結！
[ﾏｲｸ]巳厘野衆ﾁｰﾑの式神を➡
Team Shirino's shikigami
was instantly eradicated!
一瞬にして
消し炭にしてしまった!!
Soan has lost his will
to fight and run away!
[ﾏｲｸ]層安選手 戦意喪失で逃亡!!
[ﾏｲｸ]残るは 道満選手だけと
なってしまいました!!
Only Doman remains!
道満!!
Doman!
Seimei...
(道満)清明！
Seimei!
清明!!
Rin, Pyo, To, Sha, Kai,
Jin, Retsu, Zai, Zen!
臨！ 兵！ 闘！ 者！
皆！ 陣！ 裂！ 在！ 前！
Mystic counter!
Mantra of Victory!
Mystic seal!
Spell return!
A furious exchange of blows!
[ﾏｲｸ]両者 壮絶な撃ち合い!!
[ﾏｲｸ]会場が耐え切れません！
The arena is falling apart!
It's like we're watching Dragonball!
[ﾏｲｸ]まるで
｢ﾄﾞﾗｺﾞﾝﾎﾞｰﾙ｣のような光景です！
くっ！ 清明… 負けぬ…！
Seimei, I will not lose!
ｵﾚは 負けぬぞ!!
I will never lose!
It's futile, Doman.
ﾑﾀﾞじゃ 道満｡
ｷｻﾏ一個の力では ﾜｼには勝てぬ!!
Your power alone will not
be enough to defeat me!
ぐわぁ～っ!!
namaH sarvatathaagatebhyaH
sarvamukhebhyaH, sarvathaa traT...
[ﾏｲｸ]しかし 道満選手！
But Doman is already chanting
another spell!
[ﾏｲｸ]負けじと さらに
呪文を詠唱する!!
興奮して 周りが見えなくなるのが
道満 ｷｻﾏの悪いｸｾじゃ｡
You have a bad habit of getting so excited that
you lose sight of everything else, Doman.
今 その目 さまさせてやる！
I'm going to wake you up!
黙れ～!! 不動明王火界咒!!
Silence!
Acala Vidyaraja!
Wow!
[ﾏｲｸ]あ～っと！ 道満選手の周囲に
燃えさかる無数の呪符が!!
Doman is surrounded by
a swirl of flaming wards!
[ﾏｲｸ]たった一人で
これだけの呪符を！
To cast so many wards simultaneously!
[ﾏｲｸ]恐るべき呪力だ!!
Such an amazing display of power!
清明！ 無数の炎に焼かれ
灰になるがいい！
Seimei...
I shall incinerate you with an
infinite number of flames!
道満｡
Doman.
ｻﾊﾞを読むな｡
Don't make up numbers.
呪符103枚は
四捨五入しても 無数ではない｡
Rounding 103 wards wouldn't
give you an infinite number.
ちなみにﾜｼのは 1,562枚｡
I should mention that I'm using 1,562.
これも無数には ほど遠いの｡
Nowhere near infinity.
What an incredible number!
[ﾏｲｸ]な… なんという数だ!!
Seimei has surpassed Doman
by controlling an infinite...!
[ﾏｲｸ]清明選手
道満選手を上回る膨大な…｡
Correction, by controlling 1,562 wards!
いや…
1,562枚の呪符を操っている！
[ﾏｲｸ]まるで
炎でできた 巨大な壁だ!!
It's almost like a giant wall of fire!
Seimei... You...
せ… 清明… ｷｻﾏ…！
道満 これが ﾜｼとお前の➡
Doman, this is the difference
between our heart's wish!
想いの差じゃ!!
うわぁ～っ!!
Overwhelming!
[ﾏｲｸ]圧倒的!!
Now that Seimei has unleashed
his true power,
[ﾏｲｸ]真の力を解放した
清明選手を前に➡
道満選手
まったく太刀打ちできない!!
Doman is unable to fight back!
[ﾏｲｸ]巨大な炎にのまれた 道満選手！
Doman has been swallowed
in a giant flame to burn!
[ﾏｲｸ]その身を焼かれていく！
これは 勝負あったか～!?
Is the match over?!
((道満… 道満｡
Doman...
道満 何をやっている｡
Doman, what are you doing?
You're so hopeless.
しようがない子だ｡
また 夜更かしして｡
Staying up late again.
だって 寝れないんだもん｡
But I can't fall asleep.
Very well.
しかたない｡
I shall tell you another old tale.
また 昔話でも聞かせてやろうか｡
わ～い！ 今日は 何の話？
金太郎の外道丸退治？
Yay! What are you going
to tell me about today?
Kintaro slaying Gedomaru?
Or Momotaro?
それとも 桃太郎の…！
いや｡
No, I have an older story to tell you.
今日の話は
それより もっと昔の話だ｡
むか～し むかし
京に 悪い神様が住んでいました｡
Long, long ago, an evil
god lived in the capital.
The brutal god, Antenmaru, shrouded
the capital in dark clouds
闇天丸という その鬼神は➡
京の空を暗い雲に包み
雨ばかり降らせて➡
人々を苦しめていました｡
and tortured the people
with an eternal rain.
しかし この闇天丸を
京に現れた２人の旅人が➡
However, Antenmaru was sealed by the
mysterious power of two travelers.
不思議な力で
封じ込めてしまったのです｡
京の空は晴れ
皇は彼ら兄弟に お礼として➡
The skies cleared above the capital and the emperor
showed his appreciation for the brothers
京を護る者の意を込めた➡
by granting the name Mikado, as protectors
of the capital, and made them his servants.
御門という姓を与え
家来としたのでした｡
御門兄弟は とても仲がよく➡
The Mikado brothers were very close,
２人の前では どんな怪異も➡
and they were able to drive away
all forms of wickedness.
たちどころに
逃げ去っていきました｡
Their strong bond kept the capital safe.
２人は強い絆により
京を長らく護り続けたのです｡
でも 妖でさえ切れない
彼らの絆に➡
But something happened to fracture their bond,
where demons had been unable to strike.
ﾋﾋﾞが入る事件が起きました｡
御門兄弟の弟は皇の妹君➡
The younger Mikado brother was in love with
the emperor's sister, the lovely princess.
美しき姫に
密かに思いを寄せていました｡
でも 姫と御門兄弟とでは
身分が違いすぎました｡
However, the princess lived in a different
world from the Mikado brothers.
The younger brother's love was
a sad one that could never be.
弟の恋は決して
叶うことのない悲しい恋でした｡
The younger brother kept his feelings
for the princess secret
弟は姫への思いを胸にしまい➡
as he could only watch
over her from afar.
ずっと遠くから
彼女を見守ることしか➡
できなかったのです｡
That was when a shocking piece
of news reached his ears.
そんな折 弟の耳に
驚くべき知らせが届きました｡
The princess had been kidnapped.
姫が何者かにさらわれたのです｡
姫をさらったのは➡
The kidnapper was...
兄でした｡
His older brother.
Yes, the older brother was also
in love with the princess.
そう 兄も弟と同じく
姫に思いを寄せていたのです｡
Sadly, they had fallen in love with each other
without the younger brother knowing
悲しくも弟の知らぬ間に➡
兄と姫は
互いに思い合う仲となり➡
and eloped, abandoning their
position and prestige!
地位も名誉も捨てて
駆け落ちしたのでした｡
The emperor was absolutely furious
これに激昂した皇は➡
and declared that the older
brother be tried as a traitor.
兄を姫をさらった逆賊として
討伐命令を下しました｡
And the younger brother was
chosen to track him down.
その任に選ばれたのは弟でした｡
複雑な思いを秘めながら
兄のもとへ向かう弟｡
The younger brother set off on
his search with a heavy heart...
でも 幸せそうに暮らす兄と姫｡
But his older brother was living
happily with the princess...
And when he saw their baby, his heart
was overcome with darkness.
そして その赤子を見たとき➡
彼の心は
真っ黒に染まってしまいました｡
気がつくと弟の前には
２人が倒れていました｡
The next thing he knew, the two of them
were on the ground before him.
The two people he loved most.
彼が愛した２人が｡
赤子を見逃したのは
これ以上 自分の心が➡
He spared the baby because he could not bear
for his heart to be blackened any further.
醜く黒く染まっていくのに➡
耐えられなかったから
なのでしょう｡
彼は京に戻り
立派な官職を得ました｡
Once he returned to the capital, he was named
to a high position in the government.
But despite his prestige, despite his beautiful
wife, his heart remained clouded.
でも どんなに
立派な地位につこうと➡
どんな美しい妻を娶ろうと➡
彼の心が晴れることは
ありませんでした｡
Rain continued to fall on the
capital, as it did in his heart.
彼の心と同じように➡
京に雨が
降り続く日々が続きました｡
And the younger brother finally realized.
そして 弟は
気づいてしまったのです｡
その雨は
自分が降らせていることに｡
That he was causing the rain...
That he had become a demon...
自分が
鬼になってしまっていることに｡
The darkness had spread from
his heart to the rest of his body,
心だけでなく体までも
醜く黒く染まった その姿は➡
transforming him into the evil god he
and his brother had once sealed,
かつて兄とともに封じた
悪鬼 闇天丸そのものでした｡
Antenmaru!
闇天丸は２人に封じられた後も
隙をうかがい➡
Antenmaru had been biding his
time after they sealed him,
before possessing the younger brother through
his jealousy, hatred, and negative feelings,
弟の嫉妬心 憎しみ
負の情念をよりしろに➡
彼にとりつき ２人に復讐を
果たそうとしていたのです｡
all while plotting revenge.
However, it was too late
by the time he realized.
しかし 気づいたときには
もう遅すぎました｡
An arrow was fired into his hideous face.
彼の醜く歪んだ顔に
１本の矢が突き刺さりました｡
There stood the son of his brother,
whose life he had spared.
そこに立っていたのは
彼が あのとき見逃した➡
兄の子の姿でした｡
かくして 京を長きに亘り
包んでいた雲は晴れたのです｡
And thus, the clouds which had
shrouded the capital cleared.
However, a new dark cloud was born.
しかし 新たに生まれた
深き暗雲が１つ｡
よみがえった闇天丸
父の仇を討ち➡
The son of the older brother
slew the revived Antenmaru
and entered the Emperor's service,
founding the Ketsuno clan.
皇に仕えることとなった
兄の子が興した結野家｡
[Ketsuno]
And the children of the younger brother
who were chased from the capital
そして 父が犯した
責により姓を奪われ➡
and had their name taken,
the Shirino clan.
都落ちした
弟の子供たちが興した…｡
[Shirino]
The holy gate, Mikado, which
had once guarded the capital,
かつて 京を護った
聖なる門 御門は➡
ｹﾂとｼﾘ 汚れたﾓﾝへと➡
was split in half like a dirty ass.
真っ二つに
割れてしまったのです｡
And thus began the long struggle
between Ketsuno and Shirino.
ここに
結野家と巳厘野家の➡
長きにわたる 騒乱の火蓋が
きって落とされたのでした｡
A spiral of growing hate...
その幾重にも重なった
憎しみの螺旋は…｡
How am I supposed to fall asleep
after hearing all that melodrama?!
寝れるか!! そんなﾄﾞﾛﾄﾞﾛの
昔話 聞かされて！
これ｡
ちゃんと聞かぬか 道満｡
Now listen, Doman.
No way!
嫌だよ どうせまた晴明君と
勝負してこいとか言うんだろ！
You're going to tell me to
fight Seimei-kun again!
So it's true that you've become
friendly with the Ketsuno boy.
やはり 結野の小僧と
懇意になっているというｳﾜｻ➡
まことだったか｡
昔のことなんて知らない！
I don't care about the past!
Don't force your family feud onto us!
一族の因縁なんか
ﾎﾞｸらに押しつけないでよ！
晴明君は
とってもいいﾔﾂなんだよ！
Seimei-kun's a really nice guy!
He taught me how to curse
my enemies today!
今日だって ﾎﾞｸに
怨敵呪殺法を教えてくれたんだ｡
きっと ﾎﾞｸらの代になったら➡
Once the two of us take over, the Ketsuno clan
and Shirino clan will get along together!
結野家と巳厘野家
仲よくできる時代がくるって➡
We made a promise!
そう２人で約束したんだ！
You fool!
この痴れ者!!
ﾔﾂらに 地位も名誉も奪われた
ご先祖様の恨み➡
Can you not understand the grudge our ancestors hold
for having their position and prestige taken away?!
ｷｻﾏには わからぬか！
Get along together?
我らが 仲よくできる時代？
そんなもの
くるわけがなかろう｡
That will never happen!
怨敵に 怨敵呪殺法を
習っているﾋﾏがあるなら➡
If you have time to learn how to curse
your enemies from an enemy,
あの小僧を呪殺してこい｡
curse that boy to death.
If you don't end your
relationship with him,
ﾔﾂとの縁
切らぬというのなら…｡
our relationship as father
and son ends here.
親子の縁 切らせてもらうぞ))
What's that?!
(新八)あれは！
道満さんに刻まれた呪印が！
The mystical mark on Doman-san...!
((残念じゃ｡
It's too bad.
I thought we could become best friends.
お前とは 親友に
なれると思っていたのに｡
おい 聞いたか｡
ｳﾁの坊ちゃんがまた➡
Hey, you hear?
Our young master was beaten
up by the Ketsuno kid again.
結野んとこの小僧に
ｺﾃﾝﾊﾟﾝにやられたって｡
しかたあるまい｡
No chance there.
That kid's said to be the greatest prodigy
the Ketsuno clan has ever seen.
相手は 結野衆始まって以来の神童
と謳われているそうじゃないか｡
あの齢にして 大人でも
かなう者がいないとか｡
Adults can't even beat him,
and he's still young.
Man, what a terrifying kid.
いやはや
末恐ろしい小僧だな｡
ｳﾁの臆病なﾎﾞﾝﾎﾞﾝとは
わけが違うってか｡
Completely different from
our craven young master.
I have to worry about our future when
our next head is so pathetic.
あんな情けない次期当主じゃ
この先 不安だよな｡
Honestly, I envy the Ketsuno clan.
まったく
結野家が うらやましいね))
You fool!
((このﾊﾞｶ者が！
You have the nerve to crawl
back to this house!
よくも おめおめと
この家に帰ってこれたな｡
一族の恥さらしめ！
You have shamed our clan!
ﾔﾂに勝つまで
帰ってくるなと申したはず！
I told you not to return
until you defeated him!
もっとﾔﾂを憎め！ 妬め！
うらやめ！
Hate him!
Envy him!
Despise him!
We are armed with a millennia of malice!
一千年にわたる
怨嗟の念こそ 我らが武器！
Change that hatred into power!
憎しみを力に変えろ！
たとえ 鬼になろうとも➡
Take everything back, even if it requires
you to become a demon!
ﾔﾂらから
すべてを奪還するのだ！
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい｡ ｳﾁのお兄ちゃん
手加減ってものを知らなくて｡
My brother doesn't know
how to hold back.
Oh no...
いけない…
お尻から血が出てる｡
You're bleeding from your butt.
私の使って｡
You can use mine.
Help one another when in need, right?
["Rorie"]
[Note: This is a play on "Laurier",
a woman's sanitary napkin brand.]
困ったときは
お互い様だもの))
[ﾏｲｸ]こ これは何だ!?
What is this?!
[ﾏｲｸ]道満選手の顔に
刻まれていた文字が➡
The writing on Doman's
face is spreading!
体中に広がっている！
[ﾏｲｸ]あ あれは!!
That's?!
Doman.
(闇天丸)道満 我に身を委ねよ｡
Surrender your body to me!
ﾔﾂらは ぬしらを 陽の下から➡
The ones who banished your family from
the light to the dark should be hated!
陰へと追いやった 憎むべき相手｡
滅すべき相手｡
Should be destroyed!
何を迷う？ 何を戸惑う？
Why do you hesitate? Why do you wait?
一千年前 あのときのように
我に身を委ねればよいのだ｡
Surrender your body, just as it happened
a thousand years ago!
((ごめんなさい｡
I'm sorry...
Today's that day...
今日 私 …なの))
Recall!
(闇天丸)掘り起こせ お前の
奥底に眠る 憎しみのﾏｸﾞﾏを！
The magma of hatred
sleeping deep within!
((お～い ｸﾘｽﾃﾙ｡
紙が切れた｡
Hey, Christel.
We're out of paper.
は～い じゃあ
ここ置いておきますから))
Okay, then I'll leave some out here.
That's all you ever have!
こればっかりじゃねえか～!!
(闇天丸)お前から
すべてを奪った連中を許すな｡
Never forgive the ones who
took everything from you!
If you can never have what you want,
どうせ 手に入らぬのなら
すべて壊してしまえ｡
destroy it all!
闇に染まれ！
Soak into darkness!
ど… 道満｡
式神を己が身に宿したのか！
Doman...
Did you channel yourself
into a shikigami?
No.
(外道丸)違う｡
That is not a mere shikigami.
あれは式神なんて 生やさしい
もんじゃないでござんす｡
清明様 どうやらあの男…｡
Lord Seimei, that man...
Has allowed his hatred to drive him
into summoning something terrible.
憎しみのあまり
とんでもないもんを この世に➡
呼び起こして
しまったようでござんす｡
まさか… あれは!!
Don't tell me that's...?!
(外道丸)一千年前
結野衆と 巳厘野衆が➡
The most evil of gods, sealed by
the Ketsuno and Shirino clans
a thousand years ago
after a desperate fight.
決死の思いで封じた最強の邪神➡
闇天丸でござんす｡
Antenmaru.
あっ… 闇天丸だと…｡
Antenmaru, you say?!
The demon who almost destroyed
the capital a thousand years ago...
一千年前 京を壊滅の
危機に追いやった鬼｡
我らが祖 御門一族と
幾度に亘って戦いを繰り広げ➡
The strongest of the wrathful gods which
was sealed by our predecessors,
ようやく封じられた
最強の邪神が…｡
the Mikado, after many battles...
なぜ ここに!?
Why is it here?!
It was revived.
よみがえらせたでござんす｡
あの男 負の情念にとらわれ
力を求めるあまり➡
That man was driven by negative
feelings to seek power
外法に手を出したでござんす｡
and dabbled in the forbidden arts.
封印されていた
闇天丸を呼び起こし➡
He's awakened the slumbering Antenmaru
and given his own body.
己が身に
宿らせたのでござんしょ｡
Turn his own body over to a demon...
鬼を自分の身に｡
あやつ 何てﾏﾈを…｡
How could he do this?
You intend to repeat the tragedy from
a thousand years ago, Doman?!
一千年前の悲劇…
再び繰り返すつもりか 道満｡
道満様！ しっかりしてくだされ！
いったい 何が…｡
Lord Doman! Get a hold of yourself!
What's going on?!
No! He can no longer differentiate
between friend and foe!
いかん！ 敵と味方の
区別もついておらん！
皆 逃げろ～!!
Everyone run!
Wake up! Doman!
目を覚ませ！ 道満!!
法術が効かな…｡
My spells don't work!
Lord Seimei!
(葛葉)清明様！
(神楽)新八！
Shinpachi! We don't have
time to worry about rules!
もう勝負うんぬん
言ってる場合じゃないね！
(２人)うお～!!
(葛葉)闇… 清明様の法術をも
飲み込む圧倒的な闇の力｡
Darkness...
Overwhelming darkness capable of even
swallowing Lord Seimei's spells...
道満の負の情念をくらい
さらに力を増している｡
It consumes Doman's negative
feelings to grow stronger.
It can no longer be stopped...
もう… あれは
誰にも止められない…｡
すべてを闇で覆うまで
あれは 止まらない…｡
It won't stop until it has shrouded
everything in darkness!
清明様！
(清明)来るな！
Lord Seimei!
Stay back!
外道丸 葛葉 その男と
その者たちを連れて逃げろ！
Gedomaru! Kuzunoha!
Take that man and his
friends and escape!
清明様！ くっ… 外道丸!?
Lord Seimei!
Gedomaru?!
あきらめるのは
まだ早いでござんす｡
It's too early to give up.
まだ… この男がいるでござんす｡
This man has yet to play his role.
なっ… 何を言ってるの｡
What are you saying?!
早く治療の続きを｡
右のﾀﾏは ほぼ治ったでござんす｡
Continue treating him.
His right ball is more or less healed.
清明様でさえ
太刀打ちできなかったのよ｡
Lord Seimei wasn't able to
stand against that thing!
こんな ﾀﾏなし男に
何ができるっていうの｡
What could this man with
no balls possibly do?!
確かに ﾀﾏはないでござんす｡
It's true that he has no balls...
でも この男は… 心に…｡
But this man...
...has a soul that can never be crushed.
決して 潰れぬﾀﾏが
ぶら下がっているでござんす｡
何やってんだい ｱﾝﾀ…｡
ﾑﾁｬしちゃいけないよ！
What are you doing?!
Don't push yourself!
Your left ball is still crushed!
ｱﾝﾀ まだ左のﾀﾏが潰れたまま…｡
(銀時)ﾀ… ﾀﾏなら➡
It's just as she said, I'm good to go...
もう ｿｲﾂの言うとおり
間に合ってらぁ｡
ﾊﾞﾗﾝｽよく頼むぜ…｡
Help keep my balance...
Speaking of which,
it's time for me to use this baby.
ﾀﾏときたら お次は…｡
ｺｲﾂだろ｡
鬼とﾗﾝﾃﾞﾌﾞｰ決め込んでくる｡
めかしこんでくれや！
Got a rendezvous with a demon.
Spruce it up a bit.
あの汚ねえｹﾂに
ぶちこめるくらいの➡
Something flashy enough
to stick up its dirty ass!
立派なもんを…｡
ぐわぁ～!!
What are you doing?!
(神楽)何やってるｱﾙか お前ら！
もう 敵だ 味方だ
言ってる場合じゃないね！
There isn't time to worry about
which side you're on!
このままじゃ
結野家も 巳厘野家も➡
At this rate, the Ketsuno clan, Shirino
clan, and all of Edo will be wiped out!
全部 引っこ抜かれて
江戸は 何にもなくなっちゃうね！
力を貸すｱﾙ！ 仲が悪くたって➡
Help him out!
You may have had your differences,
but you were all trying to protect Edo!
お前ら 江戸を守ろうとする
目的は一緒ね!!
逃げろと言ってるのが
わからんのか！
Didn't I tell you to escape?!
妹萌え！ 待ってるね！
今すぐ 助けるｱﾙ！
Sister lover!
Hold on!
We're coming to help!
これも 結野と巳厘野に
生まれた者の定めだ｡
This is the fate of those born
to Ketsuno and Shirino.
どれだけ あがこうと➡
We may struggle, but we cannot
escape a millennia of karma.
一千年前から続く 因果の輪から➡
抜け出すことは 叶わぬ｡
かつて ﾜｼらの祖も
１人の女を奪いあい 滅びた｡
Our ancestors destroyed one
another over a woman.
Our ancestors took from yours,
and threw you into the darkness...
ぬしらの祖から
大切なものを奪い➡
闇へとおとしめたは 我が先祖｡
また 同じ過ちを ﾜｼは
繰り返してしまったんじゃな｡
And I have repeated that mistake.
うわぁ!!
だが 道満 こたびの戦い➡
However, Doman...
I can not allow a woman to
die because of our fight!
女を死なせるわけにはいかぬ｡
そして 道満
ｷｻﾏも死なせはしない｡
And Doman...
I won't let you die!
死ぬるは ﾜｼ１人で十分じゃ｡
I am the only one who needs to die.
道満… お前が ｸﾘｽﾃﾙに
惚れておったのは知っていた｡
Doman, I knew that you
had fallen for Christel.
そんな思いと ﾜｼへの敵愾心｡
That you were suffering from the mess
created by your feelings for her,
一族の圧力｡
animosity toward me, pressure
from your clan, and whatnot.
さまざまな思いに身を絡まれ
お前が苦しんでいたことも｡
きっと
取り除けると思っていた｡
I thought I could ease your suffering...
これで ３人が笑える時代がくる｡
A time would come where the three of us could
laugh together, that's what I thought...
そう思っていた｡
だが 結局 ﾜｼは…
ｸﾘｽﾃﾙも お前も➡
But in the end, I only hurt
Christel and you...
傷つけただけじゃった｡
ままならぬなぁ 道満｡
Fate is beyond our control, Doman.
たとえ 千の法術が使えても➡
I may know a thousand different spells,
友達と仲直りする術ひとつ➡
but I don't know a single way
to make up with a friend.
ﾜｼは知らんのじゃ｡
お前を そんな姿になるまで
追い込んだのは➡
I was the one who pushed
you into that state.
このﾜｼじゃ｡
ﾜｼには お前を
受け止める義務がある｡
It is my duty to take it all in.
憎しみ 悲しみ
お前のすべてを ﾜｼにぶつけよ｡
Throw me all your hatred, sadness...
お前の闇 ﾜｼが すべて受け止める｡
I'll accept all of your darkness.
一千年続いた ﾊﾞｶげたｹﾝｶ｡
My life would be a cheap price to pay to
end this stupid thousand-year-long fight...
ﾜｼの命ひとつで
終わらせられるなら安いものじゃ｡
これで すべて終わりにしよう｡
Let's end this, Doman.
道満 すべてを壊し➡
You must not lose yourself like your
ancestor and attempt to destroy all!
自分をも失った祖が過ち
繰り返してはならん｡
そこから戻ってこい！ 道満！
Come back to us, Doman!
思い出せ｡ お前が惚れた女は➡
Remember!
Was the woman you loved meant to
stand in the rain under a dark sky?
暗き空の下で
雨に濡れる女であったか？
お前が惚れたｸﾘｽﾃﾙは…｡
Was the Christel you loved...?
ﾜｼらが愛したｸﾘｽﾃﾙは！
The Christel we loved...?
Seimei-san!
清明さ～ん!!
御門が末裔よ➡
Descendant of Mikado.
もう何もかも 遅い！
It is too late.
Your voices cannot reach him,
now that I have swallowed him.
我に飲まれたきゃつには
もはや 誰の声も届かぬ｡
己が闇にとらわれた 鼠輩めが！
I laugh that a weakling consumed by darkness
would ever think to control my power.
我が力 使いこなそうなど
笑わせる！
だが こやつが負の情念｡
実にいいよりしろとなった！
However, his negative
feelings served useful.
ありがたく 頂戴するぞ｡
I'll gladly be taking them.
これで 結野と巳厘野➡
And thus, Ketsuno and Shirino, the two despicable
Mikado bloodlines, have been destroyed.
忌まわしき御門の
正統な血筋は消えた！
However, my thousand-year-long
curse will not end!
だが 一千年にもわたる我が呪い
これしきでは消えぬぞ！
我を封印せし 御門一族の血➡
I will not allow a single
drop of Mikado blood,
responsible for sealing me,
to exist in this land!
この地上に 一滴たりとも残さぬ！
What?!
(闇天丸)なっ?!
ｷｻﾏは…｡
Who are you...?!
ただのﾌｧﾝだ｡
Just a fan.
[To Be Continued]
[Preview]
Not losing to the rain.
Not losing to the wind.
Not losing to the storm.
All while never losing that smile.
"That's How I Wish To Be,
Beautiful And Strong."
[Gintoki, blast away Antenmaru and the feud
between the Shirino and Ketsuno clans,
to get Ms. Ketsuno smiling again!!]
[Next time, the conclusion of the Onmyoji arc.]
[See you next time.]